[
  { "id": 1, "question": "Who once brewed hundreds of litres of wine in a bathroom?", "answer": "Jakob" },
  { "id": 2, "question": "Who participated in the Swedish National Championship in the card game UNO in 2023?", "answer": "David" },
  { "id": 3, "question": "Who spent weekends at circus school as a child?", "answer": "Frida" },
  { "id": 4, "question": "Who handed flowers to the Queen as a child?", "answer": "Deborah" },
  { "id": 5, "question": "Who once fought in medieval armour for fun and fitness?", "answer": "Denise" },
  { "id": 6, "question": "Who performed in spandex for 200 people — three times?", "answer": "Johan" },
  { "id": 7, "question": "Who worked as a music producer?", "answer": "Adam" },
  { "id": 8, "question": "Who travelled the world interviewing gamers?", "answer": "Henrik" },
  { "id": 9, "question": "Who got yelled at by a princess?", "answer": "Diego" },
  { "id": 10, "question": "Who messaged Jonas Sjöstedt while living in Vietnam, asking to have a beer in Ha Noi, later joined him and his wife for an after-work gathering, and was invited by them to several ambassador parties?", "answer": "Hanna" },
  { "id": 11, "question": "Who has a twin sister?", "answer": "Tindra" },
  { "id": 12, "question": "Who grew up on Gotland, also called Öjn?", "answer": "Thomas" },
  { "id": 13, "question": "Who got invited to Temptation Island casting?", "answer": "Jennie" },
  { "id": 14, "question": "Who, in their early twenties, had the unusual side hustle of working as a paid DJ at an underground club in Gothenburg?", "answer": "Sandra" },
  { "id": 15, "question": "Who has competed in archery?", "answer": "Malin" },
  { "id": 16, "question": "Who was stuck on Bali during the Covid lockdown?", "answer": "August" },
  { "id": 17, "question": "Who used to breakdance and once performed a show at Heron City?", "answer": "Emilio" },
  { "id": 18, "question": "Who competed in Europe’s official snowball fighting championships?", "answer": "Emma" },
  { "id": 19, "question": "Who practiced figure skating from an early age until the age of 18?", "answer": "Fanny" },
  { "id": 20, "question": "Who is Sweden’s fastest 35-year-old?", "answer": "Dennis" },
  { "id": 21, "question": "Who worked a summer job as the Phantom in Fantomenland at Parken Zoo in Eskilstuna??", "answer": "Anders" },
  { "id": 22, "question": "Who suddenly joined a dolphin show in Spain with zero prep?", "answer": "Sandra" },
  { "id": 23, "question": "Who collects a hat from every country visited?", "answer": "Elias" },
  { "id": 24, "question": "Who jumped the world’s highest bungy?", "answer": "Tove" },
  { "id": 25, "question": "Who, at the age of eight, wrote their own play, directed rehearsals with classmates, oversaw the making of costumes and sets (even if they were a bit B-class), and whose teacher liked it so much that they went on a small tour to perform it at other schools?", "answer": "Ida" }
]